http://www.pirch.com/privacy

Privacy Statement to our Customers in the United States
We understand that visiting a company's web site or doing business by email, phone, fax or direct (postal) mail requires trust on your part. We value this trust, and if we collect or use information about you, we will do so in a responsible manner consistent with this Statement.
This page describes how PIRCH and its brands handle information we learn about customers in the United States.Your consent and preferencesWhat kind of information does PIRCH collect?What are cookies, web beacons, and log files?How does PIRCH use and disclose information about me?California Residents: Your California Privacy RightsHow To Exercise Your Rights Regarding Your Personal Information?How will PIRCH make changes to this policy?How does PIRCH secure my personal information?What about the security of linked sites?Information Collected from Children Under the Age of 13.EU and Swiss Safe HarborYour acceptance of PIRCH's privacy practices.
Your consent and preferences
PIRCH may, from time to time, contact you with communications regarding our products or services. These communications may come from PIRCH or one of its brands, and may involve product information, marketing or promotions, research, and/or other topics. To contact you, PIRCH and its brands may use the information you provide to us, including e-mail, direct (postal) mail, fax or phone. You may, at any time, inform us that you do not want PIRCH and its brands to contact you by sending your request to our Privacy Officer using the contact information below. You may also opt-out of promotional e-mail communications from one of our brands by clicking on a link provided in that brand's promotional e-mail message. However, please note that you cannot opt-out from all communications, as PIRCH may need to send you information related to our products (e.g. warranties, service reminders, etc.), your orders or accounts, etc.
What kind of information does PIRCH collect?
PIRCH collects two types of information: Personal information and aggregate or "combined" information. Personal information is data specifically about you, which you typically provide on a voluntary basis. You have the right to not supply personal information. Aggregate or combined information includes data that is related to you but studied as a group and does not identify you specifically. You cannot "opt-out" from having aggregate information collected.
What are cookies, web beacons, and log files?
Cookies: Cookies are small text files that we may store on your computer to help us identify your computer the next time you visit or to enable some functions on our web sites. PIRCH's third party service providers and business partners may also use cookies to collect nonpersonal information from visitors to our sites. We may use such information to measure the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns and web sites. If you are not comfortable with our use of cookies, please review your browser software to learn how it may be set to notify you when you receive a cookie or to reject all cookies. However, disabling cookies may limit some functionality and your experiences on our web sites.
Web beacons: Web beacons are miniscule electronic image files that can be embedded within a web page or included in an e-mail message, and are usually invisible to the human eye. When used, web beacons (also known as "clear GIFs" or "tracking pixels") may tell us such things as: how many people are coming to our web sites, whether they are one-time or repeat visitors, which pages they've viewed and for how long, how well certain online advertising campaigns are converting, and other similar web site usage data. When used in an e-mail, web beacons can tell us the time the e-mail was opened, if and how many times it was forwarded, and what links users click on from within the e-mail message. Based on this information, we can adjust the content, products, services, and promotions we provide you to better meet your interests, as well as make you aware of PIRCH products, services, and/or special offers in which you may be interested.
Log Files: These are files that record web activity and gather non-personal statistics about your visit to or use of our web sites. Log files may help us capture, among other things: (i) your IP Address, which is a unique set of numbers assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider (ISP) (note that, depending on your ISP, the number assigned to your computer can be different every time you connect to the Internet); (ii) the type of browser and operating system you use; and, (iii) other information about your online session, such as the URL you came from to get to our web site and the date and time you visited our web site. In addition to using this information to better understand how our web sites are used, we may use information captured through log files such as an IP Address (together with your personal information) to troubleshoot technical problems, maintain online safety and security, and if necessary, prohibit or restrict access to our Online Services by certain users.
Interest-based Advertising: We allow trusted third parties to place advertisements for our products and services on sites operated by others. These trusted third parties will use cookies and web beacons to measure the effectiveness of our ads and to determine the display of content and advertising to you based on your interests both on our site and other sites that you may visit. To support this interest-based advertising solution, we and the companies we have contracted with may use anonymous information about your visits to our and other web sites. The information collected and used by this process is always anonymous and does not enable any third party to identify you individually. If you would prefer not to receive our interest-based advertising, you can opt out of this activity at the Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA) website(http://www.aboutads.info) by clicking here.
How does PIRCH use and disclose information about me?
Unless otherwise stated at the point of collection, PIRCH may use your personal information for several reasons, including but not limited to, fulfilling orders, informing you about product service and warranty issues, sending you marketing communications, auditing and improving upon the level of service we provide to our customers, etc. Regardless of what may be said at the point of information collection, PIRCH reserves the right to contact you in the event of a service notification for your registered appliance, or to issue other notices concerning the safety of your appliance regardless of your stated privacy preferences. PIRCH uses aggregate information only as anonymous grouped data to better understand how visitors use our site, such as the pages most frequently viewed, the paths visitors use while navigating the site to optimize the experience, and to count the number of visitors.
PIRCH may disclose your information to third parties acting on our behalf, such as call center operators, shippers, servicers, people who analyze data for us, etc. While these third parties have access to some of the information PIRCH may have about you, the information is limited to what they need to know to do their jobs. PIRCH may disclose and share your information with our brands, such as the ones listed at the beginning of this policy. If PIRCH sells an affiliated company or other business asset, we reserve the right to transfer your personal information in connection with such a sale. Also, PIRCH may disclose your information as necessary (1) if we determine a web site or policy violation has occurred; (2) if we believe such disclosure is necessary to identify, contract or bring legal action regarding injury or interference with the rights and property of PIRCH; (3) to respond to judicial process and in cooperation with law enforcement agencies, or as otherwise required by law; and (4) to assist us in fraud prevention or investigation.
California residents: your California privacy rights
If you are a resident of California, you have the right to request from businesses a disclosure of data collection and sales practices in connection with your data. This includes: categories of personal information collected, the source of the information, use of the information and — if the information was disclosed or sold to third parties — the categories of personal information disclosed or sold to third parties and the categories of third parties to whom such information was disclosed or sold.
As a California Resident, you are afforded:
The right to request a copy of the specific personal information collected about you during the 12 months before your request
The right to have such information deleted (with exceptions)
The right to request that your personal information not be sold to third parties, if applicable
The right not to be discriminated against because you exercised any of these rights
How To Exercise Your Rights Regarding Your Personal Information?
You may request a disclosure report regarding your personal information and/or request that your personal information be deleted from our database. To make this request, please email us at optout@pirch.com. Please note, we take security measures to identify our consumers to a reasonable degree of certainty prior to providing any information or processing requests.
How will PIRCH make changes to this policy?
From time to time, we may update this Policy. If we do, we will note near the top of this page the date that any changes are made and/or when they become effective. If the changes being made are material (that is, we make a major change in the important points of the policy), we may alert you to the changes in a more prominent way. For example, we may temporarily highlight the new or revised sections in this Policy, temporarily post a prominent notice on our home page or registration/login page, or temporarily add the word "Updated" to the title of this Policy and any hypertext links pointing to this Policy. In some instances, we may also send you an e-mail message or other communication telling you about the changes and any choices you may have or actions you can take before they go into effect. Your inaction or continued use of our Online Services after any such alerts or notices, or your acceptance of any changes for which we require your prior approval, will tell us that you agree to these changes. If any changes we make will affect, in a material way, the way we treat any personal information collected directly from children/students, we will first contact parents (or, in the school context, the appropriate educators) and obtain the required form of consent.
How does PIRCH secure my personal information?
PIRCH is committed to maintaining the security of the data you provide us and will take reasonable precautions to protect your personal information from loss, misuse or alteration. Please note that there is always some risk in transmitting information over the Internet. We do use secure connections on our web sites to protect credit card information during its transmission.
What about the security of linked sites?
Some of our web sites may contain links to web sites owned by other companies. Because PIRCH has no control over the privacy practices or content of these linked sites, we recommend that you carefully review the privacy statement of each site you visit. PIRCH is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of sites owned by other companies.
Information collected from children under the age of 13
Our website and applications are aimed at a general audience and PIRCH does not generally seek to collect information about children under the age of 13. If we offer an app or website feature that collects information about a child under age 13, we will detail the type of information that we collect and how we use and disclose that information. We will obtain parental consent before we collect, use, store or disclose any personal information about a child under the age of 13. A parent or guardian of a child may contact us to request that we delete such information, if any, from our records. To do so, contact our Chief Privacy Officer.
EU and Swiss Safe Harbor
PIRCH complies with the U.S. – E.U. Safe Harbor framework and the U.S. - Swiss Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union and Switzerland respectively. PIRCH has certified that it adheres to the U.S – EU and Swiss – EU Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. Information regarding both the E.U. and Swiss Safe Harbor Frameworks can be found at: http://export.gov/safeharbor.
If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact TRUSTe at https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request. Please click here for fax and postal mail information. TRUSTe's Dispute Resolution process is only available in English.
By Postal Mail:
PIRCH Support Center3817 Ocean Ranch Blvd Suite 115 Oceanside, CA 92056
By E-mail:
optout@pirch.com
If we make photocopies of information related to your request, we reserve the right to recover related photocopy charges.
Your acceptance of our privacy practices
By using this web site or any other PIRCH web site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Statement. This Privacy Statement applies only to information provided by or collected from customers in the United States and is not intended to describe data handling procedures for information collected by other linked web sites or business partners.
We reserve the right to change or update this Privacy Statement at any time.
To Top
Kitchen. Bath. Outdoor. Joy.
Join the conversation
:
Stay in touch
Helpful Information
Contact Us
Service Request
Kitchen
Bath
Outdoor
Laundry
Back
Where should we add this?
You don’t have a project. Please create one to add the item.
Add spaces.
Add any spaces you have big ideas for.
+-
Kitchen
+-
Bath
+-
Outdoor
+-
Laundry
+-
Other
Describe your spaces.
Name your spaces if you'd like, if not we'll take care of it for you.
Success!
Name has been successfully added project(s).
My Project
Cancel
Add a New ProjectAdd a New Space Add to Space
Describe Space Add New Spaces
Keep Exploring
Back
Step 1 of 4
What do you have in mind?
Remodel an existing home, furnish your new one, or just spend some time daydreaming.
Remodel
New Home
Daydream
Step 2 of 4
Personalize your project.
Bring your PIRCH project to life by giving it a name, ideal completion date, and a color code so you can always find it easily.
Completion Month
Completion Year
Step 3 of 4
Add spaces.
Add any spaces you have big ideas for.
+-
Kitchen
+-
Bath
+-
Outdoor
+-
Laundry
+-
Other
Step 4 of 4
Describe your spaces.
Name your spaces if you’d like, if not we’ll take care of it for you.
Back
I don’t want to add any spaces right now. Skip
Project Type
Personalize
Select Spaces
Describe Spaces
Next
Start Dreaming
Back
Change project type.
Update your project with your new ideas.
Remodel
New Home
Daydream
Change project name.
Bring your project to life by giving it a name.
Change project date.
When is your ideal completion date?
Month
Year
Change project color.
Pick a color that suits your project.
Add or remove spaces.
Add the spaces you have big ideas for.
+-
Kitchen
+-
Bath
+-
Outdoor
+-
Laundry
+-
Other
Describe your spaces.Removing a space will remove any products added to that space.
<a class="pure-button wg fill-to-top save-space" ,href="#">Save Changes
Back
+-
Kitchen
+-
Bath
+-
Outdoor
+-
Laundry
+-
Other
<a class="pure-button wg fill-to-top save-space" ,href="#">Save Changes
Back
Forgot your password?
Happens to the best of us. Enter your email and we will send you a link to reset your password.
Thanks.
We’ll send you an email with instructions to reset your password shortly.
<button class="pure-button wg fill-to-top send-password btn_next" ,href="#" data-disabled-on="0" data-enabled-on="0" data-visible-on="0">
Next
Done
Back
Reset your password.
Choose a password you’ll always remember and enter it below.
Your Password Must Contain
At least one symbol (@#%$&, etc.)
Minimum 8 characters
<a class="pure-button wg fill-to-top send-password" ,href="#">Set Password
Back
Choose your password.
Choose a password you’ll always remember and enter it below.
Your Password Must Contain:
At least one symbol (@#%$&, etc.)
Minimum 8 characters
<a class="pure-button wg fill-to-top send-password" ,href="#">Set Password
Back
Start a service request online.
After submitting your request, someone from our team will be in touch.
We only service appliances purchased through PIRCH and are within our service areas.
Continue
* If you prefer to talk to someone, or need help immediately, just call: (858)966.3636, option 3
Respond during weekday standard business hours.
Step 1 of 2
Start a service request online.
We'd like to get a little more information to provide the best help we can.
Person submitting the request:
Step 2 of 2
Start a service request online.
Please tell us as much about your appliance as possible. The more we know, the better we can help. (Note: PIRCH does not service plumbing-related issues. Please contact your local plumber for any plumbing needs.)
Date Installed.
Month
Day
Year
Date Failure was Identified.
Month
Day
Year
Installed by PIRCH?
Select One
Please give us a brief description of the problem.
Got it! Thank you.
Someone from our team will be in touch shortly.
Back
Next
Next
SubmitDone
Back
Contact Us.
Call Me Back.
To find out more please see our Privacy Policy. Learn more
Preferred showroom
Interested in ...
Please provide more details.
Thanks for your message.
We’ll be in touch soon.
Submit
Done
Back
Sign in to PIRCH.
Your PIRCH account allows you to save and share projects.
Sign in with Facebook
Sign in with Google
Or sign in with your PIRCH account.
Back
New here? Sign up!
Sign In
Create Account
Back
Jeffery Sears, CEO
The great thing about PIRCH is lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, lorem ipsum.
Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipisicing elit. Ut delectus error minus at accusantium voluptate illo dolor provident, sed natus nesciunt a commodi non quae praesentium. Ad pariatur nesciunt iure, doloremque praesentium ducimus, fuga quis, dolores maxime vitae id dignissimos!
Numquam, dolorum, fugiat. Odio nisi quidem doloremque dicta, consectetur, repellat odit alias cum. Aperiam ratione nobis architecto, necessitatibus. Delectus libero inventore ullam placeat sunt asperiores provident vero deleniti, est eligendi nostrum ducimus unde, sed doloribus officiis. Repudiandae ducimus eaque tempora.
Numquam, dolorum, fugiat. Odio nisi quidem doloremque dicta, consectetur, repellat odit alias cum. Aperiam ratione nobis architecto, necessitatibus. Delectus libero inventore ullam placeat sunt asperiores provident vero deleniti, est eligendi nostrum ducimus unde, sed doloribus officiis. Repudiandae ducimus eaque tempora.
Numquam, dolorum, fugiat. Odio nisi quidem doloremque dicta, consectetur, repellat odit alias cum. Aperiam ratione nobis architecto, necessitatibus. Delectus libero inventore ullam placeat sunt asperiores provident vero deleniti, est eligendi nostrum ducimus unde, sed doloribus officiis. Repudiandae ducimus eaque tempora.
Back
Delete project?
Are you sure you want to delete this project?
Delete Project
Keep Project
Back
Create your PIRCH account.
Your PIRCH account allows you to save and share projects. Don’t worry we will never share your information with anyone. We hate spam too.
Sign in with Facebook
Sign in with Google
Or create an account with your name, email, and ZIP.
Your PIRCH account is almost ready.
You will receive a confirmation email from PIRCH momentarily. Once you confirm your email address, you can start building the home of your dreams with PIRCH or attend one of our many free classes at your nearest showroom.
Already have an account? Sign In
Create Account
Done
Back
All Showrooms
Orange County
California
View Showroom
Step 1 of 2
Make an appointment.
We’d like to get a little more information to help make your appointment more productive. To find out more please see our Privacy Policy. Learn more
Choose your areas of interest. (Optional)
Step 2 of 2
Make an appointment.
Choose your preferred time and location below. Due to current COVID-19 related social distancing and sanitation guidelines, we will reach out to confirm the final appointment time with you.
Showroom Location
Appointment Time
You’re all set. We’ll see you soon.
We will reach out to you shortly in order to confirm your appointment time. We look forward to getting to know you.Showroom tips
Back
NextSubmitDone
Back
Make an appointment.
We’d like to get a little more information to help make your appointment more productive. Please select
a showroom below to get started. Due to current COVID-19 related social distancing and sanitation
guidelines, we will reach out to confirm the final appointment time with you. To find out more please see our Privacy Policy. Learn more
Los Angeles
Glendale
Orange County
Costa Mesa
San Diego
La Jolla
Palm Springs
Rancho Mirage
NC San Diego
Solana Beach
Back
You’re all set. We’ll see you soon.
Due to current COVID-19 related social distancing and sanitation
guidelines, we will reach out to you shortly in order to confirm
your appointment time. We look forward to getting to know you.
Back
Step 1 of 3
Select event type.
Let us know what type of event you want and how many are in your party.
Class Type
Number of Guests
Event info (Cooking Class)
Price:
$50/person
Session Time:
2 hrs
Participation:
Hands-On
Guests:
10 people (min.), 12 people (max.), ages 6 and up
Options:
Add an additional hour for a buffet reception on the Patio ($250)
Note:
1 adult escort is required for every 3 attendees under the age of 14
Step 2 of 3
Request a date.
Preferred Showroom
Preferred Time
Step 3 of 3
Enter personal info.
Number of Guests
Thank You.
Thank You.
Our Events Team will be in touch soon to chat through your event request.
Back
Next
Done
Back
RSVP to
Would you like to bring a guest?
Additional Guests
This number will only be used by our Baristas of Joy to call and confirm your reservation
Oops! Looks like you have already signed up for this class within the last 30 days. To keep these classes complimentary and available for everyone to enjoy, we kindly request you limit your RSVP to once every 30 days.
We can’t wait to see you.
When you arrive, please check in at the Bliss Café. We look forward to getting to know you.
Check out the showroom ahead of time to get a lay of the land.
Submit
Done
Back
Are you sure you want to cancel?
By canceling, you will also be cancelling the RSVP for any additional guests you added.
Sorry to hear you can’t make it.
We went ahead and cancelled your RSVP. We hope to see you at a future class.
Check out other upcoming classes.
Cancel RSVP
Keep RSVP
Done
Cancel RSVP
Done
Back
Edit Account Info
It’s okay to send me (very occasional) emails about PIRCH.
Phone Type
Mobile
State
Alabama
Preferred Showroom
San Diego
Save Changes
Back
Oooops…
An error occurred, please try again later.
Close
Back
They are going to love it.
Copy link
Copy Link
Back
Back
Headline
Detail
Back
Sign Up For PIRCH Emails
Learn about the newest products for your kitchen, bath or outdoor living and be the first to hear about promotions and events featuring the world's best brands. To find out more please see our Privacy Policy. Learn more
Thanks,
Keep an eye on your email because we’re going to be sending you PIRCH updates and info soon.
Sign Up
Close
Back
Please validate your account
Please check your email to set your password before continuing
Sign Out
Facebook
Pinterest
Copy Link
